lee yon e
kim yong gwan
and also Park Yoon Woo
poton kama ice
all names and events are fictitious
any coincidences are random
drug use is a crime
which entails the destruction of personality
and also negatively affects your 7 and the environment
10 years ago, come on again
korean national university
state painting competition
you didn't pass the qualifying stage drink up drink up
drink up
how are you really
everyone out of the way
well, the handsome guy gives
what are you doing
how are you
get up
why are you climbing?
to a foreign monastery with its own charter
don't interfere, I understand
or not
you're visiting
drink it all and I'll let you go
what is there to think about?
then drink to the dregs, drink to the dregs
ladies and gentlemen look at this guy
cool how about that
everything's fine
hey
get out
well man
damn what's wrong with him
lay down to rest
hey
hey listen
I'm an idiot, I told you so
that he's an idiot
no no we just drank beer
it means you brought drugs and the deceased was your friend
everyone at your party is pointing at you
let's confess
her mother said
that she won’t give up her daughter at 7 with a killer and canceled the wedding
Tuen want to break the contract thinking
that you set up Khverim
Dad's company is about to go bankrupt
and all because of you
hyuk it's true
no I'm begging
then why were you the only one with drugs in your blood?
I've had enough
we won't see each other again
today on the occasion of the sixtieth birthday of the chairman
tuyen group kangunama
in the center of siul
the most prominent businessmen and political figures gathered
a special surprise for the hero of the day
was a touching reunion with his grandson
Kan Khverim who came to his grandfather's birthday
despite studying abroad
many business analysts still note the likelihood
introducing Khverim into the company into a leadership position
however, 1 of the officials present at the event noted
what kangu
paid special attention to family business
continuity of generations
and did not deny the possibility of introducing his grandson into the council in the future
throughout the holiday
The hero of the day himself was full of strength and energy
demonstrating to all the people his excellent health
and great mood
you haven't changed at all
found me 6 years later and you assure me again
that it's not you
I know you don't believe me
but I'll prove it to you
as through his absurd plan
tengroup kiosk on the corner
ok let us interest austin
Let's find an auditor and everything will go according to plan
what did you plan
but to get trade unionists we need a minimum
5/10 percent of shares of Tuyen Group
can you imagine how much it costs 8 1000000000
do you want
get your father's money
I would then begin to tell everything about myself about help
so be it
where will you get so much money
there is 1 here
option to earn extra money
episode 9
can you answer
how did it go
something happened
where are you picking up the phone?
nothing important
continue well
as I said
preparation of documents for a child’s education abroad
will take a long time
if you're in a hurry
you can start with language courses
but for this you will need to get a study visa
are you planning to go with your daughter?
art gallery golden canvas
how do you look at it
to tell him
I don't even think who you are
I'll run away from you
I'll get some land
tuan groups
oh you
how are you related to james
let's confirm we have a business relationship
what
I'm a supplier, he's a seller
art gallery
golden canvas
give me time
where is the money you told the ins everything
you both are finished
you won't do anything to us
let's check
where is my money
I said it's not your money
kill me and that's the end of everything
Do you think there are no more drugs in the world?
only for my product
you can get money here and now
you want money
I also know very well what I am capable of
believe me
I said call the police
if I'm not back in 10 minutes
it's fun with you
yes
decided that I had come
empty handed
you both want this product
I'll sell it to you
2 1000000000
consider it a gift
apparently you don't understand
if I needed a product
I would have taken it long ago
it means he decided to shift the risks onto us and has money in his pocket
that won't work
pay and get out
I can burn your house down
how do you like this
then no substances
where are you now
we have problems
inspectors came
agree quickly
until I changed my mind
you're crazy, do you even know who he is from the police?
he has 1000 and 1 ways to harm us
and you wanted to lead me
I had everything under control
you just had to wait a little
and how much did you promise to find out the blackmailer?
while I'm collecting money
I had to spend money on my husband's treatment
I work day and night
I can't even buy food
daughters even then
what was earned through backbreaking labor has disappeared somewhere
and you conspired with this guy
but you
but you finished me off
you
who knew my situation best
and still did this to me
I'm not
you misunderstood
Apparently I shouldn't have trusted you
I trusted this guy
who is guided only by his goals
I'll explain everything to you
let me tell you
why did I do this
too late
today is December 1, 2021
We begin the interrogation of police captain Chant Haegu
Captain Chant Haegu is in place
and he's not, he's away
what happened
notification of inspection
who is sergeant choi gyeongdo
and this is me asking you to come with us
Gwangnam District Police Station
and you
dokuman is fantoma
recently sent komuta sorok milyon vun in bitcoina
if you look here
On the 29th from someone else's account on the same day in Choi Gyeongdo
withdrawn the same amount
it's not the same money
you must be doing something
also
We have your correspondence with Juan Dong Hyun
who was a subordinate of the dokyuman
it's not mine, why did you decide that?
he was in your desk what
it happened
some kind of misunderstanding
the phantom has an informant
the name is the stitcher
ask dokuman
dokyuman never saw his face
monetary transactions were carried out anonymously
for such cases
I'll explain everything to you
this is how it really was
there was no such thing
where would I get that amount of money?
even my deposit for the apartment is much less
no it's true
captain chan gave me 10,000,000 in cash
and then lent another 30
because I'm having money problems right now
maybe someone else saw it then
how captain chan throws money left and right
I knew that kendo had problems with the mortgage
but I couldn’t even imagine that he took money from a phantom
it's all my fault
as his boss I had to help him
so you have no witnesses
no evidence
look here according to the documents
which captain chan voluntarily provided to us
last year
he had to transfer the car and apartment to his wife's name
and almost the entire salary goes to alimony
and he denies giving you money
no information
confirming
your words
but if you're right
it means captain chan framed 1 of his subordinates
why would he set you up
tell us
let's think of something else
detective pack
하
Don't treat Kanensa as a loner
most likely someone is behind her
Choi Gyeongdo
Sergeant Choi
it was him
chandhegu
the beast should have given the goods earlier
personal details of kim min
he's obsessed with your product
next loan payment date
25 0 2021
fee amount 2,300,000 won
Happiness Consumer Loan Bank in November
we guarantee an interest rate of 1 whole 60 percent up to 4000
happy street
house 55 green gate
blanket in the bedroom
what is this
me
you don't need much
I will return everything to you
oh you hey
why captain chan
think about your wife and son
what do they have to do with it?
your account must have already been frozen
behave yourself
if you want to save
at least compensation
it will be better for your family
oh yeah, what else has he done?
nothing everything is fine
don't worry
everything is fine
I told you
be more careful
아
and the lawyer prepare the documents by tomorrow
yes yes get rid of everything unnecessary
yes
of course
youngest
yes it's me if nothing happens today
I'll cut you short
got it
yeah ok
don't relax too much
after the exam read books okay
and tell me later
was it possible to contact those who were absent?
ok, you've done well, bye bye
yoojeong
oh you don't need it
please stop unhook don't go
dear beloved
my dear wait
beloved dear
sua
why didn't you come
wow of course
my jinhee
jenhee when will you come to school
entrance for fire trucks
no parking
director kan devil
아
let's continue in the same spirit
yeah but a couple of days later
convict
I can burn your house down
how do you like this
everything is fine insulin
hi are you waiting for me
yes congratulations on creating the exam
you're smart
looks like it turned out well done
what do you want to eat
try oh you
you have a lot of fun
you passed the final interview, congratulations
brother
ok you're accepted really show me
hwang dong hyun
we were amazed by your abilities during the interview
We are happy to inform you
that you have been accepted into our company I have been accepted
old fart walked into me with an ashtray
because I sold a couple of shares
what are you talking about I sold a couple of shares
to buy a dose and what
how much and what will you buy them back
forget it give me mint
otherwise I'll die
oh jamb
Somehow my hands don’t obey me at all
oh nothing
I will contact my partner with
1 lady came here as a partner
I was trying to sell everything to me
I guess I overpaid you
I even had to buy your doodles
he himself said that it’s easier to launder money through tokens
I don’t remember, it’s all annoying
who brought the goods
that and money
got it
how does she know kankhverim
who is guided only by his goals
show hidden apps
location tracking
legen kanansu
I underestimated this madam
damn
hyuk
hyuk quickly check the account of president tuan
Khvirim also has shares
why is he so animated?
when it comes to promotions
and you bought a lot
once you know the meeting schedule
hello mr kan
provide me with a list of our shareholders
Sainte Privat School of Art
I checked the timesheet
my GPA went up
this is amazing sua
but Jinha has 0 passes
she doesn't go to school
I heard from the girls
who live nearby
that her mother was fired and her father left
Jenhee herself doesn't respond to messages
I can’t understand everything
yes jenha's mom did wrong
but there is also a villain in this story
if there is a buyer
that is, the seller is right
you're crazy, look at the traffic lights
or what, daughter?
how are you
forgive me
it's all because of you
where is the money
mom
what are you doing
I'm something
thought about my
what's happening to you
you're weird
and it's true
Sainte Privat School of Art
and it was you who said something
what do you want to study there
your favorite artist went there
if only I could
and if you can go
part time job there is time
I'm mom I have a meeting here
let's talk at home
with whom
sua
bye bye
I just found out about this
the problem is
that President Toen bought even more shares
then we will need at least another 1000000000 won
we barely scraped together 5/10 of a percent
but otherwise
even together with Austin and minorities
we will not exceed the share of kangunam shares
Austin said he won't invest anymore
The main thing for him is to make a profit
where can we get 1000000000 won in a couple of days
from me more than 200000000
don't wait, I was thinking of taking a debt from sunjun konstra クション
but to me
you can't interfere
I'll do whatever I can
just give up
we were unable to soberly assess the situation
you and me
we've done enough
I'll go
I need to go with my father to work
he
I was worried about the last meeting
sooner or later your father will forgive you
even if you don't take revenge
you woke up by the way
where did your guardian go?
your father is your guardian
he rushed right away
how we told him about you
oh my god where are you
father father father
forgive me, I will definitely fix everything
I swear father
I promise you father
I promise you
father
dad
trust me
I
I won't give up
Seoul Prosecutor General's Office
Mungan University Disciplinary Committee
We ask you to come to the meeting at 10:00
December 2, 2021
divorce notice
signature yon musok
I'm home
mom
sleeping pills
mom mom
mom
mom wake up
ambulance station
Tujin you understood what I said
yes definitely
tell this to your wife
and come together to your next hospitalization
darling how are you
god
dear mother what's wrong with her
she took a big one
dose of sleeping pills
take her to the department
dear miyeon dear beloved
miyeon
why such questions
my wife has nothing to do with jenha's mom
Of course they are not directly related
you want to say
they are somehow indirectly related
that's what I would like to know
bring an umbrella, I'm on my way
we will wash out the stomach, close us
mom what will happen to mom
she will die mom will die
I forbid her to die
run home and bring her things
clothes and documents
mommy
it's all because of me
run
ㅎㅎ
you probably didn't know
the time was short
I'm sorry
where are you? something happened
we're really going to be evicted, darling
I'm bleeding and my stomach hurts, answer me
please tell Hwangjun hyung's loved ones
that he woke up
let them come
God I was scared studying in the USA
I'm more
I wanted to know how you are doing
how is gin doing here and what is this
gathered abroad
seriously why suddenly seek treatment
and didn't even tell me
and I have to
no
of course it's your business
thanks for the help
but these are family matters
and money
in America they don't provide insurance
don't worry, I'll figure it out myself
this is my husband and my daughter
goodbye, we'll call you again
study abroad
Application must be submitted 4-6 months before the start of training
spending for 1 time
and even more than 2 1000000000 won
how so
where is the tsua passport
hi again the door was open
what does the doctor say
what are you doing, my dear
where is the international passport
looks like they made a new one
why do you need him
send tsoa abroad
Tsoa is leaving
yes
sua you understand
she's a great opportunity
I don't want to deprive her of her chance
so I decided in a rush myself
It's not just you who decides everything
investment immigration
fee after 5 years of residence $800,000
you want to leave too
yes, that’s why I had to pick up my medical card
explain where you got 2 1000000000 and why
why do the police think you are involved in the incident?
with jenha's mom
Are we running away?
what have you done
I
plane tickets sul seattle departure December 4, 2021
this night
yeah I didn't want to rush
but circumstances
here you are
I have already paid for your housing and car
everything is in your name
and then you will go to this language school sua
so that you get a visa and can receive treatment
so darling
then genie you said so
I'm never wrong please
trust me again
do as I ask
I'll explain everything to you later
speak now or I'll stay
just do as I say
it's all for us
please just shut up and listen
damn
why are there no photos of me?
I'm not here
thanks for the help
but these are family matters
this is my husband and my daughter
I'll soon become a billionaire of course
and someday I will live here
and go to the local bathhouse every day
sauna with ice room
just to go straight into the cold
the streets aren't enough for you
and I’ll make a warm toilet
daughter
why doesn't she answer the phone
the subscriber cannot answer your call now
I agree let's make a deal
I'll send you the address
partner
the subscriber cannot answer now
to your call
please leave
convict
yes if you come
I'll buy you the last chance
çırts
come here to myanja
Kelson street 455
restaurateurs
art gallery golden canvas
sorry remember me
I'm talking about Hwang Jun hyung
I was told he came to his senses
where is he now
you understand
thank you for helping
it won't last long
I didn't want to miss out on a great offer
any time
this rise is near your house of course
very dangerous it's really marmalade
I think it's a sleeping pill or something for weight loss
we don't need it
By the way, where will you spend your money?
secret
we're great
Until tomorrow we will buy takpacks with our own money
bye bye
plane tickets seoul seattle
departure December 4, 2021
누구세요
yes
so we are there
daughter
Gwangnam District Police Station
witnesses in drug use case yang miyeon
Sergeant Choi Gyeongdo
boss
the police are always faithful to the law
the subscriber cannot answer your call now
please leave a message
youngest
sorry
I want to declare this
driving to danger
thin ice
because of you
she became like this
now my condition is James, quickly leave
you know, maybe we're even similar
mom why
he will never let us all go
who will touch my daughter and 7 me
I'll kill everyone
translated and voiced by the studio
mobile television ordered by online cinema ivi
in 2025